likita Chauhan

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

OBJECTIVE

I am currently on the journey to seek and secure a graphic design or similar position internship and gain experience and knowlege to move forward with my college life and professional career. I have been working and aquiring new skills and particularly do well in a team environment

GET IN TOUCH WITH ME



469-360-2342



nikita.chauhan12@yahoo.com



in/nchauhan25

EDUCATION

The University of Texas at Dallas BA, Arts and Technology Design and Production August 2017 - (expected) May 2020

Texas Tech University BFA, Art Incoming August 2016 - May 2017

ADDITIONAL SKILS

Adobe Certified Associate - Illustrator Adobe Certified Associate - Photoshop Laser engraving/cutting Silhouette Cameo 3

EXPERIENCE

Needle in a Haystack

Designer/Typesetter

August 2015 - Present

Create typesets and proof as well as printed orders as small as 10 to as big as 300 or more cards, sometimes with envelopes and even reply sets

Answer the phone and assist customers with their questions or concerns about their orders

Create vector artwork to send to vendors for outside orders as well as occasionally digitize artowrk that customers have brought in

City of Garland - Aquatics/Garland Swim Program Swim Instructor/Gatekeeper

June 2013 - August 2017 (seasonal)

Trained and tested by Jeff Ellis Management swim standards to teach children as young as 3 years to as old as 15 as well as some adults to swim, along with instructing parents to teach their babies in our Parent-Tot classes

Right hand to the supervisor, doing paperwork and assisting in making sure other instructors were able to teach and step in if needed

Watched the gate to assist patrons with questions and concerns about our program when they approached

Altitude Trampoline Park

Court Monitor/Co-Party Host

January 2018 - May 2018

Observed the court areas where I was assigned and made sure patrons were following rules as well as assisted them

Assisted the party host with the party parents and patrons to ensure everything went smoothly and all patrons had waivers and wristbands as well as check in and out party guests.

PROGRAMS

Illustrator	90%
Photoshop	75%
InDesign	70%
Word	80%
PowerPoint	90%
Excel	50%